You can lean on your elbows there.
そこにさ、ひじついてもっかい
Put this foot down.
こっちの足を下ろして
difficult?
難しい?
Just take this one down.
こっちだけ下ろして
Get on your elbows.
ひじついて
yeah?
ん?
It's nostalgic.
懐かしいって
picture?
え?
That's fine.
いいじゃん
picture?
え?
what up?
どうした?
Are you playing?
遊んでる?
Cute though.
可愛いけど
yeah?
ん?
picture,
え、
hang on.
待って
Try it.
して みよ
Look.
ほら
I haven't.
してない
This rubber is thick.
分厚いよ、このゴム
I haven't.
してない
picture?
え?
Look, look.
ほら、見て
I haven't.
してない
Haven't you?
してない?
I want you to press it.
押してほしい
I put it in like this.
このまま入れたね
I want you to wear rubber.
ゴムしてほしい
yeah?
ん?
I want you to wear rubber.
ゴムしてほしい
What have you never done?
何までしたことないの?
There isn't.
ないんだ
Well, start today.
じゃ、今日始めてね
No?
だめ?
Yeah.
うん
Well, I'll take it outside.
じゃ、外に出すから
Well, that's not the problem.
え、そういう問題じゃない
Isn't that the problem?
そういう問題じゃないの?
That's not the problem.
そういう問題じゃない
That's the problem, right?
そういう問題でしょ
Rubber.
ゴムして
Well, just for a moment.
じゃ、一瞬だけ
Only the tip.
先っぽだけ
Can I just put in the tip?
先っぽだけ入れていい?
No.
ダメ
No?
ダメ?
It's just the tip.
先っぽだけだよ
No.
ダメ
No way.
ダメな
No.
ダメ
Okay, I'll put the rubber on later.
じゃ、 後でゴムつける
No.
ダメ
Just a little bit, really.
ちょっとだけさしたほんとに
please.
お願い
Please forever.
一生お願い
I heard it earlier.
さっきも聞いたよ
Because it's only for a moment.
ほんとに一瞬だけだから
I'll put the rubber on later.
後でゴムつけるから
No.
ダメ
That's fine.
いいじゃん
No.
ダメ
I'll put it on later.
後でつけなって
It's okay as long as you don't let it out inside.
中にも出さなくて大丈夫だって
Don't worry.
安心して
Believe me.
信じておれ
Hey.
おい
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいっしょ?
hey?
ね?
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいっしょ?
Just for a moment.
もうちょっと一瞬だけ
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Just leave your hands behind your back.
そのままさ、手を後ろにして
Just keep your hands behind your back.
そのままさ、手を後ろにしたまま
Raise your feet.
足上げて
Put it between your hands and legs.
手、足の間に入れて
Put it between my legs.
俺の足の間に入れて
Spread your legs.
足広げて
Now, just lean your upper body completely forward.
じゃあ さ、上半身だけ完全に前に倒れて
Only the upper body collapsed completely.
上半身だけ完全に倒れて
Completely collapse.
完全に倒れてね
Oh, no, no.
あ、違う違う
Only the upper body.
上半身だけ
Hmm, I was surprised.
うーん、びっくりした
Raise your hips.
腰上げて
Legs, raise your hips as your legs.
足、足として腰上げて
Only the upper body fell down.
上半身だけ倒れて
how?
どうやって?
Completely collapsed.
完全に倒れて
Rest upside down.
上前にして休む
Ah, desk, is this what you mean?
あ、机こういうこと?
It felt so good that I said I wouldn't write it down.
気持ちよくて、書き出さないと言ってたから
I told you to take me outside.
外に出してって言ったわ
hey.
ね
It felt so good.
気 持ちよすぎて
Because it's okay.
大丈夫だから
It's not okay.
大丈夫じゃない
Because it's totally fine.
全然大丈夫だから
It's not okay.
大丈夫じゃないよ
I said I'd take it outside.
外に出すって言ってたのに
Eh, where are you going?
え、どこ行く?
picture?
え?